(Leonard:)-We came to apologize.
-Again.
(Leonard:)And bring you home.
Pack up your stuff and we'll head back.
(Leonard:)No. This is my home now.
(Leonard:)Thanks to you, my career is over.
I will spend the rest of my life here...
(Leonard:)...trying to teach evolution
to creationists.
(Mrs Cooper:)You watch your mouth, Shelly.
(Mrs Cooper:)Everyone's entitled to their opinion.
(Sheldon:)Evolution isn't an opinion, it's fact.
(Mrs Cooper:)And that is your opinion.
(Sheldon:)I forgive you, let's go home.
[CHUCKLES]
(Mrs Cooper:)Don't tell me prayer doesn't work.
(Leonard:)How about that?
Finally caught a break.
(Leonard:)Uh-huh.
[PENNY CHUCKLES]
(Leonard:)You know how they say
when friends have sex it can get weird?
(Sheldon:)Sure.
(Leonard:)-Why does it have to get weird?
-Pbbt. I don't know.
(Leonard:)I mean, we were friends
and now we're more than friends.
And we're whatever this is.
But why label it, right? I mean--
(Leonard:)It is what it is and--
(Penny:)-Leonard?
-Yeah?
(Penny:)-It's weird.
-Totally.